cruisesonly.com 2002-06-04

# MyTravel.com

**_MyTravel_ \- ONLINE PRIVACY STATEMENT**

_MyTravel_ is committed to respecting your privacy. Our websites are designed so that you can visit _MyTravel_ or any of its subsidiaries on the Web without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. Once you opt to provide personally identifiable information (any information by which you can be identified), it will only be used to support your customer relationship with us. 

This Online Privacy Statement regarding the privacy of the information you provide online covers five main areas: Awareness, Choice, Access & Accuracy, Security, and Oversight. 

**Awareness**   
_MyTravel_ provides this Online Privacy Statement to inform you about our privacy policy and the practices and choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. This notice may be accessed from any area of _MyTravel's_ web site. 

**What we collect**   
On some _MyTravel_ web pages, you can order travel services, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are name, contact and billing information, transaction, and credit card information, and frequent flyer numbers. 

_MyTravel_ also utilizes interactive devices on its site to create a sense of "community" and to provide its site visitors with the benefit of exchanged travel information. These interactive devices may include, but not be limited to, chat rooms, message boards, forums and similar devices. _MyTravel_ shall not be responsible for the online exchange of customer data through these means between its customers. _MyTravel_ will, however, maintain these devices to be free of objectionable, profane or inappropriate online behavior. 

In order to personalize our subsequent communications to you and continuously improve our services, we may also ask you to voluntarily provide us with information regarding your personal or professional interests, demographics, experience with our travel services, and contact preferences. _MyTravel_ uses your information to better understand your travel requirements and to provide you with better service. Specifically, we use your information to help you complete a transaction, to communicate back to you, to update you on services and benefits, and to personalize our web site for you. Credit card numbers are used only for payment processing and are not retained for other purposes. 

From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research or to provide you with marketing information we think would be of particular interest. At a minimum, we will always give you the opportunity to opt out of receiving such direct marketing or market research information. In some circumstances, we will permit you to opt in before receiving unsolicited messages. 

**Who we share it with**  
 _MyTravel_ will not sell, rent, or lease your personally identifiable information to third parties. Unless we have your permission or are required by law, we will only share the personal data you provide online with other _MyTravel_ subsidiaries that are acting on our behalf to complete the activities described above. Such _MyTravel_ subsidiaries, including those located in other countries, are bound by our privacy policies with respect to the use of this data. 

**Choice**   
_MyTravel_ will not use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the purposes described above without letting you know and offering you a choice. As previously stated, we will also provide you the opportunity to let us know if you do not wish to receive unsolicited direct marketing materials from us and we will do everything we can to honor such requests. 

Should we ever in the future share your information with third parties that are not acting on our behalf and governed by our privacy policy, _MyTravel_ will secure your permission before sharing your information with any such third parties. 

**Access & Accuracy**   
_MyTravel_ strives to keep your personally identifiable information accurate. We make every effort to provide you with online access to your registration data so that you may update or correct your information at _MyTravel's_ web site where it was submitted. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you access or enabling you to make corrections. 

**Security**   
_MyTravel_ is committed to protecting the security of your information. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We use encryption when collecting or transferring sensitive data such as credit card information. 

**Oversight**   
If you have comments or questions about our privacy policy, email: 

We also participate in the Council of Better Business Bureaus' BBBOnLine Privacy Program, and comply with BBBOnLine privacy standards. Further information about this program is available.
